# Andre Doumad

# Lead Game Developer / Programmer - Nomi Studio

Laguna, CA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Andre-Doumad/90f56d1342931321

Game Developer for Unity 3D. Produced content for the Oculus, Vive, Deepoon and Viulux for five years; two and a half years under contract. Shipped a number of VR Arcade games to clients overseas. Hands on experience building projects with multiple teams. Developed and shipped Augmented Reality/AR experiences. Professional working knowledge of C#, state machines and workflow pipelines.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Lead Game Developer / Programmer**

Nomi Studio - March 2015 to Present

Program content on time.

- Prototype new concepts for research purposes.
- Maintain reliable source control.
- Program autonomously.
- Integrate assets from animators, modelers, illustrators and musicians.
- Interpret concepts from designers and incorporate them into projects.
- Produce toolsets for level designers so that they may add content to the game.
- Annihilate every last bug.

#### Co-Founder

Quantum Forge - October 2013 to Present

Publish Sol Avenger on Steam Greenlight.

- Build particle systems to represent various effects in the game.
- Complete new team objectives, coordinate schedules and ensure deadline targets are met.
- Program working passion projects.
- Run the Kickstarter and marketing campaign.

#### Information Systems Engineer

AHAP Inc - June 2005 to Present

Provide solutions for secure data transmission.

- Ensure private patient data adheres to HIPAA guidelines.
- Webmaster.

# **Data Entry**

AHAP Inc - Irvine, CA - June 2011 to 2012

Irvine, CA

Admissions and Records

Work Duration: June 2011 - 2012

- Assist students or prospective students in their endeavors enter college.
- Data Entry.
- Process Student Information.
- Work with student transcripts.

### **Technical Writer**

Virbak - 2008 to 2009

Technical Writer.

- Document robotic tape library backup procedures.
- Run various backup procedures on Linux, VMware, ESX, AIX, HP, Sun servers.
- Test the software in every configuration across many operating systems and platforms.

# Data Analyst (SQL/CATI)

Kaiser Permanente - Irvine, CA - April 2007 to August 2008

Maintained Microsoft Access System for the call center employees for Apria Healthcare.

Updated procedural documents.

### **EDUCATION**

# **Associates Degree in Computer Science in Computer Science**

Irvine Valley College

**SKILLS** 

C# (5 years), Programming (5 years), unity3D (5 years), Unreal (2 years), Rapid Prototyping (5 years)

LINKS

https://www.linkedin.com/in/andre-doumad-4361528a